<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<atom:entry xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xml:base="http://jvance.com/blog/2008/11/07/ChangeIsGoodForTechnology.atom" xmlns:svc="http://atomsite.net/info/Service" xmlns:app="http://www.w3.org/2007/app" xmlns:thread="http://purl.org/syndication/thread/1.0">
  <atom:published>2008-11-07T10:22:00-06:00</atom:published>
  <atom:title>Change is Good for Technology</atom:title>
  <atom:content type="html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img title="ChangeGov" style="border-top-width: 0px; display: inline; border-left-width: 0px; border-bottom-width: 0px; margin-left: 0px; margin-right: 0px; border-right-width: 0px" height="177" alt="ChangeGov" src="http://jvance.com/media/2008/11/07/Image12.media" width="256" align="right" border="0" /&gt; As many others, I’m very excited with the outcome of the presidential election.&amp;#160; I’m proud to support who is being called &lt;a href="http://www.opensecrets.org/news/2008/11/silicon-valley-strongly-backed.html"&gt;America's first &amp;quot;tech president.&amp;quot;&lt;/a&gt; His policies toward technology are very refreshing to a self proclaimed &lt;a href="http://www.rd.com/advice-and-know-how/are-you-a-tech-junkie-quiz/article51072.html"&gt;tech junkie&lt;/a&gt; like me.&amp;#160; Hey, I bought a &lt;a href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Core_2#Yorkfield"&gt;quad core&lt;/a&gt; as soon as they had 45 nano-meter transistors.&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;Obama’s policies can be viewed at the new website &lt;a href="http://change.gov"&gt;change.gov&lt;/a&gt;.&amp;#160; Some of the highlights of his &lt;a href="http://www.change.gov/agenda/technology/"&gt;technology agenda&lt;/a&gt; are:&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;ul&gt;   &lt;li&gt;Protect the Openness of the Internet &lt;/li&gt;    &lt;li&gt;Encourage Diversity in Media Ownership &lt;/li&gt;    &lt;li&gt;Safeguard our Right to Privacy &lt;/li&gt;    &lt;li&gt;Open Up Government to its Citizens &lt;/li&gt;    &lt;li&gt;Deploy Next-Generation Broadband &lt;/li&gt;    &lt;li&gt;Reform the Patent System &lt;/li&gt;    &lt;li&gt;Lower Health Care Costs by Investing in Electronic Information Technology Systems &lt;/li&gt; &lt;/ul&gt;  &lt;p&gt;These are great. I feel strongly about Obama working towards these goals.&amp;#160; His view on &lt;a href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Network_neutrality"&gt;net-neutrality&lt;/a&gt; is very refreshing:&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;blockquote&gt;   &lt;p&gt;The number-one priority of Obama's technology platform […] is to protect network neutrality to preserve the benefits of open communication on the Internet. The political argument surrounding Internet access is whether companies managing Internet traffic should be allowed to charge for higher speeds or capacities instead of treating all users equally. Service providers posit that charging for priority on the Internet will promote investment in networks and allow for better management of congestion caused by large amounts of digital data traveling online. Google, among other Internet firms, argues that service providers are pushing for profit that would stifle online innovation and economic growth.      &lt;br /&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&amp;quot;I will take a back seat to no one in my commitment to network neutrality,&amp;quot; Obama said during a stop at Google's California headquarters. &amp;quot;Because once providers start to privilege some applications or websites over others, then the smaller voices get squeezed out and we all lose.&amp;quot; &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.opensecrets.org/news/2008/11/silicon-valley-strongly-backed.html"&gt;-opensecrets.org&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/blockquote&gt;  &lt;p&gt;Also, I hope to see a social revolution in the way people interact with the government.&amp;#160; We should be able to directly vote on the issues rather than things being filtered through a “lobbied” congress.&amp;#160; Or at least a nationally recognized system for tracking and providing feedback to our elected officials.&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;This is a great time for us in the technology community.&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;&amp;#160;&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Disclaimer: The views represented here do not reflect the views of my employer.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;  </atom:content>
  <atom:category term="Politics" label="Politics" />
  <atom:updated>2008-12-04T05:43:05.1956666Z</atom:updated>
  <atom:id>tag:jvance.com,2008-11-07:blog,ChangeIsGoodForTechnology</atom:id>
  <atom:author svc:id="Jarrett">
    <atom:name>Jarrett</atom:name>
    <atom:email>jarrettv@gmail.com</atom:email>
    <atom:uri>http://jvance.com/</atom:uri>
  </atom:author>
  <svc:ratingCount>1</svc:ratingCount>
  <svc:ratingSum>5</svc:ratingSum>
  <app:edited>2009-06-29T21:14:02.8992407Z</app:edited>
  <svc:raters>68.113.123.204</svc:raters>
</atom:entry>